https://www.softwarepursuits.com/legal-policy/

Contact Sales: US 800.367.4823 | International +1.650.372.0900
Contact Sales
Technical Support
Legal Policy
Web Site Terms of Use
By using this web site you agree to accept these terms. If you do not accept these terms, please do not use this web site.
Use of Web Site
Software Pursuits, Inc. (SPI) authorizes you to view and download the materials at this Web site (Site) only for your personal, non-commercial use, provided that you retain all copyright and other proprietary notices contained in the original materials on any copies of the materials. You may not modify the materials at this Site in any way or reproduce or publicly display, perform, or distribute or otherwise use them for any public or commercial purpose. For purposes of these Terms, any use of these materials on any other Web site or networked computer environment for any purpose is prohibited. The materials at this Site are copyrighted and any unauthorized use of any materials at this Site may violate copyright, trademark, and other laws.
If you breach any of these Terms, your authorization to use this Site automatically terminates and you must immediately destroy any downloaded or printed materials.
User Submissions
Other than personally identifiable information, which is covered under our Privacy Statement, any material, information or other communication (“Communications”) you transmit or post to this Site will be considered non-confidential and non-proprietary. SPI will have no obligations with respect to the Communications. SPI and its designees will be free to copy, disclose, distribute, incorporate and otherwise use the Communications and all data, images, sounds, text, and other things embodied therein for any and all commercial or non-commercial purposes. You are prohibited from posting or transmitting to or from this Site any unlawful, threatening, libelous, defamatory, obscene, pornographic, or other material that would violate any law.
Links to Other Web Sites
Links to third party Web sites on this Site are provided solely as a convenience to you. If you use these links, you will leave this Site. SPI has not reviewed all of these third party sites and does not control and is not responsible for any of these sites or their content. Thus, SPI does not endorse or make any representations about them, or any information, software or other products or materials found there, or any results that may be obtained from using them. If you decide to access any of the third party sites linked to this Site, you do this entirely at your own risk.
Disclaimer
THE MATERIALS AND SERVICES PROVIDED AT THIS SITE ARE PROVIDED “AS IS” WITHOUT ANY WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND INCLUDING WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, OR NON-INFRINGEMENT OF INTELLECTUAL PROPERTY.
SPI further does not warrant the accuracy and completeness of the materials or services at this Site. SPI may make changes to the materials and services at this Site, or to the products and prices described in them, at any time without notice. The materials and services at this Site may be out of date, and SPI makes no commitment to update the materials and services at this Site. Information published at this Site may refer to products, programs or services that are not available in your country. Applicable law may not allow the exclusion of implied warranties, so the above exclusion may not apply to you.
Limitations of Liability
IN NO EVENT WILL SPI, ITS SUPPLIERS, OR OTHER THIRD PARTIES MENTIONED AT THIS SITE BE LIABLE FOR ANY DAMAGES WHATSOEVER (INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, THOSE RESULTING FROM LOST PROFITS, LOST DATA OR BUSINESS INTERRUPTION) ARISING OUT OF THE USE, INABILITY TO USE, OR THE RESULTS OF USE OF THIS SITE, ANY WEB SITES LINKED TO THIS SITE, OR THE MATERIALS OR INFORMATION OR SERVICES CONTAINED AT ANY OR ALL SUCH SITES, WHETHER BASED ON WARRANTY, CONTRACT, TORT OR ANY OTHER LEGAL THEORY AND WHETHER OR NOT ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES. IF YOUR USE OF THE MATERIALS, INFORMATION OR SERVICES FROM THIS SITE RESULTS IN THE NEED FOR SERVICING, REPAIR OR CORRECTION OF EQUIPMENT OR DATA, YOU ASSUME ALL COSTS THEREOF. APPLICABLE LAW MAY NOT ALLOW THE EXCLUSION OR LIMITATION OF INCIDENTAL OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES, SO THE ABOVE LIMITATION OR EXCLUSION MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU.
U.S. Government Restricted Rights
Government users will receive no greater than Restricted Rights as defined in FAR 52.227-19 (c) (1-2 ) (June 1987). Government users will receive no greater Limited Rights as defined in FAR 52.227-14 (June 1987) or DFAR 252.227-7015 (b) (2) (November 1995), as applicable in any technical data at this site.
Applicable Laws
This Site is administered by SPI from its offices in San Mateo, California. SPI makes no representation that materials or services at this Site are appropriate or available for use outside the United States, and access to them from territories where their contents are illegal is prohibited. You may not use or export or re-export the materials or services at this Site or any copy or adaptation in violation of any applicable laws or regulations including without limitation U.S. export laws and regulations. If you choose to access this Site from outside the United States, you do so on your own initiative and are responsible for compliance with applicable local laws. These Terms will be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the State of California, without giving effect to any principles of conflicts of laws.
Links to this Site
Anyone linking to SPI’s Web site must comply with the following rules and all applicable laws.
May link to, but not replicate, SPI content.
Must not create a browser or border environment around SPI content.
Must not imply that SPI is endorsing it or its products.
Must not misrepresent its relationship with SPI.
Must not present false information about SPI’s products or services.
Must not use the SPI logo without permission from SPI.
Must not contain content that could be construed as distasteful, offensive or controversial, and should contain only content that is appropriate for all age groups.
General
SPI may revise these Terms at any time by updating this posting. You should visit this page from time to time to review the then-current Terms because they are binding on you. Certain provisions of these Terms may be superseded by expressly designated legal notices or terms located on particular pages at this Site.
Revised September 2000
Innovative Software, Expert SupportSince 1975
951 Mariners Is Blvd, Ste 300San Mateo, CA 94404
AboutProductsSolutionsContactTechnical Support
Legal PolicyPrivacy Policy
Stay Connected
Sales800.367.4823650.372.0900Support650.372.0900
FollowFollow
Subscribe to SPI Connections for product updates and news.
SUBSCRIBE
Search for:
Software Pursuits is proud to be a
This web site uses cookies to provide you with the best online experience. By using the Software Pursuits web site, you accept our use of cookies detailed in our Privacy Policy.OkPrivacy policy
